あぁ！見て見て、何か大っきいのがある！
Ah! Look over there, there's something huge!
おぉ…何だろうね。あれ…
Whoa… I wonder what it is?
ハイッテミヨウカ。
Shall we go in?
キーラキラしてるねー。
｛It's all sparkly.｝
大きい橋だねー。
What a large bridge!
何に使う場所なんだろう。
I wonder what this place is used for.
探検だね！
It's an exploration!
ココハ…
This place is…
ア。
Ah.
イタッ。
Ow.
アワワワワワ…
Ah, ah ,ah…
うわぁ…ご、ご、ごめんなさい！
Waah… we-we-we're sorry!
アワワワワワ…
Ah, ah ,ah…
うわぁ！
Waah!
だ、大丈夫でしたか？
A-are you alright?
うわぁ、大っきい子だねー。
Wow, you're quite the large ｛｝.
そうだろう、そうだろう。サラブレッドだからね。
Indeed, indeed. It is because I am a Thoroughbred.
足もとっても速いんだぞ。
I'm also very fast.
でも今のでビックリして、どうも調子が出ないなぁ。
But that was a shocker just right now; I just can't can do it right now.
ふん、ふん！
Hmph, hmph!
ご、ごめんなさい。
I-I'm sorry.
嘘、嘘。
Nah, just kidding.
お、フレンズ！もー、ビックリしたよー。
Oh, a Friend! Gosh, you surprised us.
どうも、初めまして。
Nice to meet you.
色々と珍しいね。どこから来たの？
I haven't seen you girls round these parts before. Where are you from?
さばんなからだよ！
From the Savanna!
あの、ここって一体…
Uhm, what is this place?
ここは競馬場だよ。よかったら少し見ていくかい？
This is a racecourse. Would you like to see around?
｛はい！｜あい！｝
Yes!
綺麗な所だねー！あなたの縄張り？
It's very pretty! Is it your territory?
まあ、そんな感じかな。
I suppose you could say that.
ここは、何をする所なんですか？
What do you do here?
レース。駆けっこだね。
Racing.
ここをみんなで走るの？
You run here with everyone else?
ほっ。それも面白いかもね。
Hmm, that might be interesting.
わーい！
Whee!
お花がたくさん咲いてますねー。
The flowers are blooming very nicely!
お？
Hm?
彼女もサラブレッドで、白毛だ。
She's also a Thoroughbred. She has a white coat.
すごいジャンプ！
She has an amazing jump!
綺麗ですねー！
She's pretty!
あぁ！いつの間に…青鹿毛さん、その方達は？
Ah! Since when… Seal-brown-san, who are those girls?
かばんちゃん！次あれ、次あれ！
Kaban-chan, let's go there next!
待って、サーバルちゃん！
Hold on, Serval-chan!
あれ？珍しい子だね！あなたも食べる？
Hmm? You don't look like someone I see everyday. Would you like to eat too?
わーい！食べる、食べる！
Yeah! I'm game!
力がもりもり湧いて、ぐんぐん走れるよ！
Your strength will well up, and you'll be able to run really fast!
サーバルちゃんも、さらに足が速くなるかな。
Maybe you'll get faster too, Serval-chan.
何ここ、何ここ！
Where are we now?
大きいトンネルですねー。
What a large tunnel!
真っ暗だねー。
It's all dark!
暗い所は任せてー！
If it's dark places, you can leave it to me!
どこに繋がっているんですか？
Where does this lead to?
お楽しみ。
Just wait and see.
広ーいねー！
Wow, what a large field!
うぅー…わーい！
Whee!
よし。
Alright.
じゃあ、一勝負しようか。
Shall we have a match right now?
えぇ？
Huh?
頑張れ、頑張れー！
You can do it!
位置について…！
On your marks…
本気で行くよ。
I won't be pulling any punches.
負けないんだから！
I'm not gonna lose!
勝った。
I win.
青鹿毛速いよー。
You're fast, Seal-brown.
惜しかったね、サーバルちゃん。
So close! Serval-chan.